<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DeepSpace</string>
    <string name="nasa">NASA</string>
    <string name="asteroid_radar">Asteroid Radar</string>
    <string name="mars_rovers">Mars Rovers</string>
    <string name="spacex">SpaceX</string>
    <string name="upcoming_events">Upcoming Events</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="contact">Feedback</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="launches">Launches</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>

    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="tesla_roadster">Tesla Roadster</string>
    <string name="where_is_starman">Where is Starman?</string>
    <string name="dragon_space_capsules">Dragon space capsules</string>
    <string name="all_spacex_capsules_list">All SpaceX capsules list</string>
    <string name="cores_used_in_spacex_aircrafts">Cores used in SpaceX aircrafts</string>
    <string name="where_does_spacex_aircrafts_land_on">Where does SpaceX aircrafts land on?</string>
    <string name="launching_and_landing_pads">Launching and Landing pads</string>
    <string name="cores">Cores</string>
    <string name="capsules_list">Capsules list</string>
    <string name="dragons">Dragons</string>
    <string name="what_is_spacex">What is SpaceX?</string>
    <string name="learn_about_company">Learn about company</string>
    <string name="launch_pads">Launching pads</string>
    <string name="land_pads">Landing pads</string>
    <string name="yodo1_app_id">ca-app-pub-5580537606944457~4465578836</string>


    <string name="email_or_username">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="send_mail">Send</string>
    <string name="relogin">Please follow the link and login one more time</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_again">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="login">sign in</string>
    <string name="wrong_credits">wrong credentials</string>
    <string name="notHaveAcc">Don`t have an account yet? Sign up!</string>
    <string name="register"><u>Sign up</u></string>
    <string name="sign_out"><u>Sign out</u></string>
    <string name="auth">Authentication</string>
    <string name="registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="emptyField">This field must be filled</string>
    <string name="userAlreadyRegistered">User already registered</string>
    <string name="reg_title">Sign up</string>
    <string name="send">send</string>
    <string name="lastName">last name</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="passwordRepeatDontMatch">passwords isn\'t same</string>
    <string name="invalidEmail">invalid email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="log_in">log in</string>
    <string name="create_your_own_post">Create your own post</string>
    <string name="edit_text_hint">Start typing here</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_is_null_message">Empty title, interesting</string>
    <string name="rocket">Rocket:</string>
    <string name="first_stage">First stage:</string>
    <string name="second_stage">Second stage:</string>
    <string name="fairings">Fairings:</string>
    <string name="nasa_news">NASA news</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
    <string name="spacex_card_title">All about SpaceX</string>
    <string name="spacex_card_description">Information about launches, space capsules, how it all started and even more.</string>
    <string name="loading_error_message">An error occurred while loading the content, please check the network connection</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="click_on_the_image_hint">Click on the image to view description</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="description_upcoming">Set notifications for the dates of upcoming SpaceX launches, so as not to miss the event\'s live broadcasts, discussions and so on</string>
    <string name="space_nav">Space Navigator</string>
    <string name="default_error">An unexpected error has occurred</string>
    <string name="proximity">Proximity</string>
    <string name="rotation_vector">Rotation vector</string>
    <string name="down_line">________</string>
    <string name="sensors">Sensors</string>
    <string name="rotation_matrix">Rotation matrix</string>
    <string name="light_level">Light level</string>
    <string name="compass">Compass</string>
    <string name="gyroscope">Gyroscope</string>
    <string name="accelerometer">Accelerometer</string>
    <string name="temperature">Temperature</string>
    <string name="pressure">Pressure</string>
    <string name="source_colon_space">Source: </string>
    <string name="comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="create_post">Create post</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="company_info">Company info</string>
    <string name="company_spacex">Company : SpaceX</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="asteroid_name">Asteroid name:</string>
    <string name="user_posts">User posts</string>
    <string name="blogs">Blogs</string>
    <string name="blogs_and_news"><![CDATA[Blogs & News]]></string>
    <string name="about_app"> Dive into the world of space! Read space news, communicate with the other space-lovers and always know where planets are located at the current moment by using space navigator!</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers: </string>

    <string name="copiedToClipboard">%1$s email copied to clipboard</string>

    <string name="title_for_feedback">Title</string>
    <string name="name_for_feedback">Your name</string>
    <string name="email_for_feedback">Your contact email</string>
    <string name="text_for_feedback">Describe the complaint</string>
    <string name="button_text_for_feedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="feedback_sent">Your feedback was sent! You will be replied by email </string>
    <string name="create_by_space_colon">"Created by: "</string>
    <string name="reply_to">"reply to "</string>
    <string name="article">Article</string>
    <string name="post">Post</string>
    <string name="yana_gladkikh">Yana Gladkikh</string>
    <string name="denis_barov">Denis Barov</string>
    <string name="vladimir_abubakirov">Vladimir Abubakirov</string>
    <string name="samuil_nalisin">Samuil Nalisin</string>
    <string name="danil_khairulin">Danil Khairulin</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="unexpected_error">Произошла непредвиденная ошибка.</string>
    <string name="date">Date:</string>
    <string name="curiosity">Curiosity</string>
    <string name="earth">Earth</string>
    <string name="core">Core:</string>
    <string name="mission">Mission:</string>
    <string name="landedn_on_water">Landed on water?</string>
    <string name="blocks">Blocks:</string>
    <string name="reused">Reused:</string>
    <string name="what_are_dragons">What are Dragons?</string>
    <string name="rover_name">Rover name:</string>
    <string name="launching_date">Launching date:</string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera:</string>
    <string name="click_to_view_the_area">Click to view the area</string>
    <string name="name">Name:</string>
    <string name="vehicles_launched">Vehicles launched:</string>
    <string name="attempted_successful_launches">Attempted/Successful launches:</string>
    <string name="landing_type">Landing type:</string>
    <string name="reconnect">Reconnect</string>
    <string name="launch_mass_kg">Launch mass (Kg):</string>
    <string name="orbit_type">Orbit type:</string>
    <string name="longtitude">Longtitude:</string>
    <string name="distance_from_the_earth">Distance from the Earth:</string>
    <string name="distance_from_the_mars">Distance from the Mars:</string>
    <string name="details">Details:</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_sign_in">Already have an account? Sign in!</string>
    <string name="company_name">Company name:</string>
    <string name="founder">Founder:</string>
    <string name="elon_musk">Elon Musk</string>
    <string name="founded">Founded:</string>
    <string name="_2002">2002</string>
    <string name="employees">Employees:</string>
    <string name="vehicles">Vehicles:</string>
    <string name="launch_sites">Launch sites:</string>
    <string name="chief_executive_officer">Chief Executive Officer:</string>
    <string name="chief_technology_officer">Chief Technology Officer:</string>
    <string name="chief_operating_officer">Chief Operating Officer:</string>
    <string name="cto_propulsion">CTO propulsion:</string>
    <string name="valuation">Valuation:</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary:</string>
    <string name="address">Address:</string>
    <string name="city">City:</string>
    <string name="state">State:</string>
    <string name="california">California</string>
    <string name="astronomical_picture_of_the_day">astronomical picture of the day</string>
    <string name="mars_rover_photos">Mars Rover Photos</string>
    <string name="choose_date">Choose date</string>
    <string name="distance_from_earth">Distance from earth:</string>
    <string name="is_it_dangerous">Is it dangerous?</string>
    <string name="estimated_diameter">Estimated diameter:</string>

    <string name="mercury_description">Mercury is the smallest planet in the Solar System and the closest to the Sun. Its orbit around the Sun takes 87.97 Earth days, the shortest of all the Sun\'s planets. It is named after the Roman god Mercurius (Mercury), god of commerce, messenger of the gods, and mediator between gods and mortals, corresponding to the Greek god Hermes. Like Venus, Mercury orbits the Sun within Earth\'s orbit as an inferior planet, and its apparent distance from the Sun as viewed from Earth never exceeds 28. This proximity to the Sun means the planet can only be seen near the western horizon after sunset or the eastern horizon before sunrise, usually in twilight. At this time, it may appear as a bright star-like object, but is more difficult to observe than Venus. From Earth, the planet telescopically displays the complete range of phases, similar to Venus and the Moon, which recurs over its synodic period of approximately 116 days.</string>
    <string name="venus_description">Venus is the second planet from the Sun. It is named after the Roman goddess of love and beauty. As the brightest natural object in Earth\'s night sky after the Moon, Venus can cast shadows and can be, on rare occasions, visible to the naked eye in broad daylight. Venus lies within Earth\'s orbit, and so never appears to venture far from the Sun, either setting in the west just after dusk or rising in the east a little while before dawn. Venus orbits the Sun every 224.7 Earth days. It has a synodic day length of 117 Earth days and a sidereal rotation period of 243 Earth days. As a consequence, it takes longer to rotate about its axis than any other planet in the Solar System, and does so in the opposite direction to all but Uranus. This means the Sun rises in the west and sets in the east. Venus does not have any moons, a distinction it shares only with Mercury among the planets in the Solar System.</string>
    <string name="sun_description">The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System. It is a nearly perfect ball of hot plasma, heated to incandescence by nuclear fusion reactions in its core, radiating the energy mainly as visible light, ultraviolet light, and infrared radiation. It is by far the most important source of energy for life on Earth. Its diameter is about 1.39 million kilometres (864,000 miles), or 109 times that of Earth. Its mass is about 330,000 times that of Earth; it accounts for about 99.86% of the total mass of the Solar System. Roughly three quarters of the Sun\'s mass consists of hydrogen (~73%); the rest is mostly helium (~25%), with much smaller quantities of heavier elements, including oxygen, carbon, neon and iron.</string>
    <string name="mars_description">Mars is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet in the Solar System, being larger than only Mercury. In English, Mars carries the name of the Roman god of war and is often referred to as the "Red Planet". The latter refers to the effect of the iron oxide prevalent on Mars\'s surface, which gives it a reddish appearance (as shown), that is distinctive among the astronomical bodies visible to the naked eye. Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere, with surface features reminiscent of the impact craters of the Moon and the valleys, deserts and polar ice caps of Earth.</string>
    <string name="jupiter_description">Jupiter is the fifth planet from the Sun and the largest in the Solar System. It is a gas giant with a mass more than two and a half times that of all the other planets in the Solar System combined, but slightly less than one-thousandth the mass of the Sun. Jupiter is the third-brightest natural object in the Earth\'s night sky after the Moon and Venus. It has been observed since pre-historic times and is named after the Roman god Jupiter, the king of the gods, because of its observed size.</string>
    <string name="saturn_description">Saturn is the sixth planet from the Sun and the second-largest in the Solar System, after Jupiter. It is a gas giant with an average radius of about nine and a half times that of Earth. It only has one-eighth the average density of Earth; however, with its larger volume, Saturn is over 95 times more massive. Saturn is named after the Roman god of wealth and agriculture. </string>
    <string name="uranus_description">Uranus is the seventh planet from the Sun. Its name is a reference to the Greek god of the sky, Uranus, who, according to Greek mythology, was the great-grandfather of Ares (Mars), grandfather of Zeus (Jupiter) and father of Cronus (Saturn). It has the third-largest planetary radius and fourth-largest planetary mass in the Solar System. Uranus is similar in composition to Neptune, and both have bulk chemical compositions which differ from that of the larger gas giants Jupiter and Saturn.</string>
    <string name="neptune_description">Neptune is the eighth and farthest-known Solar planet from the Sun. In the Solar System, it is the fourth-largest planet by diameter, the third-most-massive planet, and the densest giant planet. It is 17 times the mass of Earth, slightly more massive than its near-twin Uranus. Neptune is denser and physically smaller than Uranus because its greater mass causes more gravitational compression of its atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="pluto_description">Pluto (minor planet designation: 134340 Pluto) is a dwarf planet in the Kuiper belt, a ring of bodies beyond the orbit of Neptune. It was the first and the largest Kuiper belt object to be discovered. After Pluto was discovered in 1930, it was declared to be the ninth planet from the Sun. Beginning in the 1990s, its status as a planet was questioned following the discovery of several objects of similar size in the Kuiper belt, including the dwarf planet Eris.</string>
    <string name="iss_description">The International Space Station (ISS) is a modular space station (habitable artificial satellite) in low Earth orbit. It is a multinational collaborative project involving five participating space agencies: NASA (United States), Roscosmos (Russia), JAXA (Japan), ESA (Europe), and CSA (Canada). The ownership and use of the space station is established by intergovernmental treaties and agreements.</string>

</resources>